Jason M. Brunelle

jason@jasonbrunelle.com ● (832) 499-1660 ● linkedin.com/in/jason-brunelle-18b6bb177 ● github.com/jasonmb626

SUMMARY

Ten years General Management experience in the movie theater industry. Recent graduate with a B.S. in Computer Science with an interest in Web Development, Network Security and Cryptography. Strong knowledge of Microsoft Office/Excel Macros. Team player with teambuilding experience. Experience juggling competing projects.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming/Languages: HTML/CSS/JavaScript (inc. Node.js), C/C++/C#, Java, VBA, Git/GitHub

Frameworks/Libraries: React, Redux Bootstrap

Database: MongoDB, PostgreSQL, MySQL, Microsoft SQL Server

Office Tools: Microsoft (MS) Word, Outlook, Excel

Operating Systems: Microsoft Windows and Linux

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF HOUSTON-DOWNTOWN - Houston, TX

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Houston Community College - Houston, TX

Associate in Arts

July 2019

GPA: 3.86

GPA: 4.00

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Landmark Theatres 2005-July 2019
General Manager - River Oaks Theatre, Houston, TX July 2009-July 2019

- Typical retail management duties including:
 - o Managed, trained, and developed staff and other management
 - o Ensured we are meeting Payment Card Industry (PCI) compliance
 - o Utilized interpersonal/business communication skills with home office employees
- Extraordinary duties beyond those of other general managers:
 - Formated to Linux standard filesystem, packaged, and distributed over 100 hard drives in external enclosures for company-wide use
 - Created/maintained multiple Excel Workbooks used to improve workflow company-wide
 - o Converted movie trailers to industry-standard digital projection for company-wide use
 - Updated/improved the official audit workbook used company-wide at direction of corporate auditor and operations department
 - Trained employees at other company sites for new opens and changes in point-of-sale software

General Manager - Dobie Theater, Austin, TX

Assistant Manager - Magnolia Theater, Dallas, TX

Floor Staff - Magnolia Theater, Dallas, TX

UNIVERSITY OF NORTH TEXAS - Resnet, Denton, TX

2005-2006

June 1999-May

2002

- Designed and maintained a secure web-interface for students to register and pay for university housing extensively utilizing HTML and JavaScript
- Designed security measures for computer labs including a suite of software including multiple front-ends and a backend
- Maintained a database of all university residents with Internet issues using MySQL
- Troubleshot problem Internet connections with end users (dormitory residents)
- Set up and maintained Linux/Apache/MySQL/PHP servers